We are in Yachiyo City, Kumamoto Prefecture.
It has a strong flavor. Very tasty.
Do you know where the little squid are?
There they are!
Now let's start cooking. First of all, I'd like to make jam.
Here are some freshly picked strawberries!
They are huge! We have about 2 kilograms here, and now we would like to measure 1 kilogram.
Okay, I'll measure one kilo.
Oh, so much jam...
1013 is OK... 1013 grams.
That's for a whole box. Next, we'll remove the stems from the strawberries.
We work in silence.
Silence continues.
Now we're done removing the stems. Next, we'll wash them.
Oh!
ha ha ha
Shouldn't it be so
I've washed it, then I'd like to measure out 200g of granulated sugar
I haven't done much baking
It's a pretty rare experience.
I will mix the washed strawberries with the granulated sugar.
After putting in the strawberries, mix them with a spatula.
Put the strawberries and granulated sugar in a saucepan and bring it to a boil over medium heat.
It's simmering down a lot.
About 10 minutes now.
Add the sugar and pectin.
At this point, I put half of the mixture through a sieve.
The point of this is to prevent lumps from forming.
The mixture is now simmering down to a thick consistency.
I would like to add 75cc of lemon juice.
Here's my own point.
I'm going to add a liqueur called cuantro.
This liqueur has an orange aroma and a slightly mature taste, so I'd like to add it.
I'm going to put 150cc of this liqueur.
Thanks for watching!
Mmm.
Oh, it's delicious!
It's so good!
But there's a little bit of alcohol
I feel like there's a little alcohol left in it.
I'm going to boil it for about 10 minutes to remove the alcohol.
Of course there is sweetness from the strawberries, but there is also a nice balance with a little sourness from the Fantoro.
It's a jam that can be used with a variety of dishes. It is very delicious.
Now let's fill the jars with jam!
Here it is!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Next, we will make the original with the stars.
I would like to make Yatsushirose!
It's called "Yatsushirose".
I used strawberries I just harvested.
and tomatoes, one of Yatsushiroshi's specialties.
And mozzarella cheese, caprese style.
I named it "Yatsushirose" because it's made with ingredients from Yatsushiroshi.
I named it "Yatsushirose" because it uses ingredients from Yatsushiroshi.
I'd like to make it that way.
First of all, remove the heft from the tomatoes.
Cut the tomatoes in half horizontally against the stem.
Yes, I've finished cutting.
Then remove the core and skin of a clove of garlic and crush it lightly with the side of the knife.
I've never done this before.
Then cut it.
Ready!
Put olive oil and garlic in a frying pan and heat.
When the aroma starts to rise, place the small tomatoes cut side down and sprinkle with a teaspoon of salt.
Meanwhile, cook the pasta.
Prepare 180 grams of noodles.
Here we go.
I couldn't do it neatly at all.
When the tomatoes are soft enough to be crushed without resistance, remove the garlic and put the tomatoes in a bowl.
Remove the garlic and crush the tomatoes.
Then add white wine and reduce to about half the volume.
Adjust the density with the pasta cooking water and let it come in.
[Fast forward.
When they are nice and packed, remove the skins and seeds and set aside.
Mix the chilled sauce with the cold-water-cured pasta.
Now that it's mixed in nicely, we're going to serve it up.
It's like this, right?
Wow!
Phew!
Isn't it good?
What? Not good?
Here we go.
Then we'll add the basil.
Finally, olive oil and pepper are added for the final touch.
The original yatsushi rosé is now ready to eat!
Now let's eat it. Bon appétit.
I wonder what it is like. For now, I would like to start with the noodles as usual.
I'll start with the noodles. It's amazing.
It's very refreshing and tasty, and since it's going to get warmer, I think it's perfect for the summer season.
It's really delicious. It has a nice acidity from the tomatoes.
The strawberries are really sweet, so I think they go well with this pasta.
Delicious!
The strawberries are really delicious!
It is sweet all the time, but not too sweet, so I think it would go well with pasta and other Western-style dishes.
It was my first time to visit Kumamoto Prefecture and my first time to visit Yaeshiro City, which is a town rich in nature.
It's been a long time since I've been to Kumamoto Prefecture and this was my first time in Yajo City, but it's a town with rich nature and the food is really delicious.
I was surprised to find that both seafood and mountain foods are delicious in Kumamoto City.
And the jam I tried my hand at making this time is now on sale in limited quantities, so I hope you'll all enjoy it!
If you are interested in Yaesu City, please visit Yaesu City and try it!
I hope you will visit Yaesu City as well. I look forward to visiting Yaesu City again.